{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your aasdasdasda",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "HTML/CSS/Javascript",
      "description": "LoremText"
    },
    {
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. ",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "name": "asdasd",
      "description": "asdasdasdasdasd!!!!",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "asd",
      "description": "asd",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "deck1",
      "description": "spades",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "name": "qw",
      "description": "qw",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "name": "ADSFDASF",
      "description": "ASDFASDF",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "name": "ASDFASDF",
      "description": "ASDFASDF",
      "id": 11
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?!!!a\n<Route>!!!\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all asdasd!!!!!!!!!a",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "Differentiate between Real DOM and Virtual DOM.",
      "back": "Virtual DOM updates are faster but do not directly update the HTML",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "How do you modify the state of a different React ",
      "back": "Not at all! State is visible to the component only.",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasdas",
      "back": "dasdasdasd",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasdasd",
      "back": "asdasdasdasd",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasd",
      "back": "asdasd",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasd",
      "back": "asdasdasd",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasdasd",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasdasd",
      "back": "aasdasdasd",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "javar",
      "back": "alex",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "a",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "aa",
      "back": "aa",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "newcard",
      "back": "newcard",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 28
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasdasd",
      "back": "asdasda",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasda",
      "back": "asdasdasd",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 31
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "front": "im front",
      "back": "back",
      "deckId": 8,
      "id": 33
    },
    {
      "front": "hello",
      "back": "goodbywe",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 34
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 35
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "c",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 36
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 37
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "b",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 38
    },
    {
      "front": "qw",
      "back": "qw",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 39
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 40
    },
    {
      "front": "asasdasda",
      "back": "asdasda",
      "deckId": 9,
      "id": 41
    },
    {
      "front": "ASDFASDFASDFAASDFSDF",
      "back": "FASDFASFDASDFASDFASDFASDF",
      "deckId": 11,
      "id": 42
    },
    {
      "front": "ASDFASDF",
      "back": "ASDFASDF",
      "deckId": 11,
      "id": 43
    }
  ]
}